Contact

jay.jbradley@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jaybradley-27264856 (LinkedIn) Teamwork.com (Company)

Top Skills

Information Technology Digital Typing

Jay Bradley

Helping teams to collaborate in a better way and be more efficient. Working together, beautifully!

Ireland

Summary

Energetic, enthusiastic and ambitious Customer Service Associate and Manager with in excess of 5 years experience within the communications industry. Team player with the ability to motivate and encourage my work colleagues. Motivated with the need to learn and strong desire to succeed. Relish a challenge and keen interest in lifelong learning. Highly technically minded and customer focused with strong engaging, selling and troubleshooting skills. Brand awareness and customer satisfaction. Pick up technology as second nature. Strong brand awareness and customer focused, taking a lot of pride in the 'Customer Experience' with a positive 'Can do' attitude. Proactive and takes initiative. Target and goal orientated.

Experience

Teamwork.com 3 years 11 months

Enterprise Account Executive
July 2017 - Present (3 years 3 months)
Cork, Munster, Ireland

Inside Sales Account Executive November 2016 - Present (3 years 11 months) Cork

HTC

Territory Sales & Training Manager June 2015 - November 2016 (1 year 6 months)

To increase brand awareness, sales uplift and advocacy of HTC products providing the interface between HTC and the retail marketplace. To build strong relationships whilst delivering key messages regarding products, ensuring compliancy and merchandising the products and brand. Responsible for individual geographic territory. Identify process gaps and solutions,

deployment and training and updates through various mediums, Onboarding and Induction of new hires.

Responsibilities Include:

- * Continuously build the HTC brand through a planned call cycle of specified retail accounts within a specified geographical territory.
- * Demonstrate new and existing HTC products and train retail staff on their benefits and features, encouraging retailers to recommend and showcase HTC products to their customers.
- * Maintain a number of training visits per working day, during normal visit cycles.
- * Establish effective relationships with store staff to ensure staff endorsement of HTC products to customers.
- * Monitor, analyse and report the implications of competitor activity within the territory.
- * Ensure in store marketing is executed as directed.
- * Support additional training sessions as requested by HTC HQ. These include, but are not restricted to, Call Centres, area meetings, corporate support.
- * In store active selling included in monthly cycle to help increase sales, motivate stores and understand the buying psychology of the customer.

Hutchinson 3G (trading as O2 Ireland) O2 Guru

October 2013 - May 2015 (1 year 8 months)

The role of the Guru is to create a 'World Class Customer Experience' instore. This is a full role which requires working with our customers in a very supportive way. Being friendly, approachable and an informal manner is essential in how we as Guru's interact with our customers. Provide expert advice and knowledge about our widerange of Products & Services and deliver the right best solution to guarantee that an exceptional customer experience is

received at all times. Overall, the O2 Guru plays a pivotal role in ensuring that the latest technologies and new products entering the market are understood and explained in a logical non jargon way to our customers. Most importantly, the O2 Guru role is to work effectively with the rest of the team to develop their understanding of new advancements in technology and assist with the overall performance and success of the store in a training, coaching and development fashion.

Responsibilities include:

- Develops self and others and embraces new ideas and ways of doing things.
- Leads the delivery of training and new product briefings to in-store team and provide regular coaching of latest industry trends, products and services.
- Attending Store Manager's Conference, Area Manager's Meetings as required.
- Reporting and feedback to the business on a regular.
- Establishing & maintaining trusted relationships with new and existing O2 Customers, creating loyalty to the network and sales opportunities.
- Articulating information and ideas clearly, logically and in a non jargon way.
- Resolves customer's complex technical issues.
- Has expert knowledge in all O2 propositions such as business, data, broadband, value added services and devices.
- Understanding all forms of 'connectivity' i.e. broadband, Wi-Fi, social networking sites, wireless, business devices etc.
- If and when required, assuming the responsibilities a sales assistant.

O2 Ireland (a Telefónica Company)
Senior Sales & Customer Service Associate
September 2007 - May 2015 (7 years 9 months)

Telefonica O2 Ireland Limited

- •Training and development of product knowledge to region. (Device Specialist)
- •Trouble shooting of handsets, laptops, broadband connection issues etc.
- •Selling services, brand and products to the customer.
- •Upholding of day to day running of store banking, Admin- updating of excel sheets, cashing up, conference calls, training etc.
- •Dealing with consumer, SPT, SME and corporate accounts in both closing of new contracrs and renewals.
- •Turning of customers into fans and building a loyal customer base.
- •Promoting the brand as the most competitive in the communications market. Proactively contributing to the expansion of the organisation, successfully growing our customer base by regularly winning new customers.
- •Effectively taking ownership of consumer, SPT, SME and corporate accounts by listening to their needs, meeting and exceeding their expectations, thereby enhancing their overall retail experience.
- •Calling existing O2 customers daily to offer the best available deals that best suite their usage to get them to recontract with the network

O2 Ireland (a Telefónica Company)
Acting Manager
July 2011 - July 2012 (1 year 1 month)
O2 Retail Wilton - O2 Ireland

- Manager of O2 Wilton 6 Months.
- •Training & development of staff and managing team performance.
- •Drive of Sales Team.
- Setting targets and goals for the team.
- Payroll and rostering.

- •Trade reports and reporting on KPI's to Area Manager and Head Office.
- •Weekly & Monthly Stocktaking.
- •Ensuring that all figures and data are entered into the companies database carefully and correctly.
- •Ensuring efficient delivery of all administrative processes connected to sales and after sales on all products and services with the use of BRIO and CRM, abiding by all company policies and adhering to legislative requirements.
- ·Banking, cash sheets etc.

Xtra-vision Ltd
Customer Service Representative
October 2005 - August 2007 (1 year 11 months)
Mitchelstown, Co. Cork

- Delivering fantastic customer service keeping the Brand of the company at the forefront at all times.
- Cross selling and Upselling.
- · Monthly Stocktaking.
- Facing off and maintaining of the wall and merchandising of the store.
- · Maintaining organisation of "the Vault".
- Ensuring efficient delivery of all administrative processes connected to sales and after sales on all products and services with the use of CRM, abiding by all company policies and adhering to legislative requirements.
- Cashing up.

Education

Cork Institute of Technology
Bachelor of Science (BSc), Computer Science (2006 - 2007)

St. Johns Central College

HIgher Certificate, Introduction to Computer Game Design · (2005 - 2006)

St. Johns Central College

Higher Certificate, Computer Networking and Web-Design · (2005 - 2006)